Guide to the Greenwich House Records TAM.139
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series II: Directors' and Executives' Records
  - Subseries A: Director (Mary K. Simkhovitch)
    - Sub-subseries 4: Correspondence -- Organizations (Alphabetical)
      - School of Applied Religion (Cincinnati)- Fletcher, Joseph, 1936 (Box 21, Folder 65)
      - Social Unit Institute/Organizing Committee of the Social Unit Plan, 1939-1944 (Box 21, Folder 66)
      - Society of the Companions of the Holy Cross, 1939, 1941, undated (Box 21, Folder 67)
      - S- Organizations Correspondence, 1938-1944 (Box 21, Folder 68)
      - T- Organizations Correspondence, 1938-1944 (Box 21, Folder 69)
      - University Settlement/ 50th Anniversary, 1936 (Box 21, Folder 70)
      - U- Organizations Correspondence, 1937-1944 (Box 21, Folder 71)
      - V- Organizations Correspondence, 1932-1944 (Box 21, Folder 72)
      - Workers' Alliance, 1938 (Box 21, Folder 73)
      - Works Progress Administration, 1937-1939 (Box 21, Folder 74)
      - Works Projects Administration, 1940 (Box 21, Folder 75)
      - Works Progress Administration- Workers' Education Project, 1936-1938 (Box 21, Folder 76)
      - W- Organizations Correspondence, 1937-1944 (Box 21, Folder 77)
      - Y- Organizations Correspondence, 1937-1942 (Box 21, Folder 78)
    - Sub-subseries 5: Correspondence -- Recommendations; Requests for employment and assistance
      - A- re Recommendations, Employment, etc., 1937-1943 (Box 22, Folder 1)
      - B- re Recommendations, Employment, etc., 1934-1945 (Box 22, Folder 2)
      - C- re Recommendations, Employment, etc., 1937-1944 (Box 22, Folder 3)
      - D- re Recommendations, Employment, etc., 1937-1943 (Box 22, Folder 4)
      - E- re Recommendations, Employment, etc., 1937-1942 (Box 22, Folder 5)
      - F- re Recommendations, Employment, etc., 1937-1943 (Box 22, Folder 6)
      - G- re Recommendations, Employment, etc., 1934-1944 (Box 22, Folder 7)
      - H- re Recommendations, Employment, etc., 1937-1944 (Box 22, Folder 8)
      - I- re Recommendations, Employment, etc., 1934-1942 (Box 22, Folder 9)
        Reel 26 (MN# 2207)
      - J- re Recommendations, Employment, etc., 1936-1944 (Box 22, Folder 10)
      - K- re Recommendations, Employment, etc., 1936-1943 (Box 22, Folder 11)
      - L- re Recommendations, Employment, etc., 1933-1944 (Box 22, Folder 12)
      - M- re Recommendations, Employment, etc., 1932-1944 (Box 22, Folder 13)
      - N- re Recommendations, Employment, etc., 1937-1943 (Box 22, Folder 14)
      - O- re Recommendations, Employment, etc., 1933-1944 (Box 22, Folder 15)
      - P- re Recommendations, Employment, etc., 1937-1944 (Box 22, Folder 16)
      - Q- re Recommendations, Employment, etc., 1938-1943 (Box 22, Folder 17)
      - R- re Recommendations, Employment, etc., 1933-1944 (Box 22, Folder 18)
      - Smith, Julia A., 1941 (Box 22, Folder 19)
      - S- re Recommendations, Employment, etc., 1938-1944 (Box 22, Folder 20)
      - T- re Recommendations, Employment, etc., 1939-1943 (Box 22, Folder 21)
      - U- re Recommendations, Employment, etc., 1940-1942 (Box 22, Folder 22)
      - V- re Recommendations, Employment, etc., 1937-1942 (Box 22, Folder 23)
      - W- re Recommendations, Employment, etc., 1935-1943 (Box 22, Folder 24)
      - Y- re Recommendations, Employment, etc., 1939 (Box 22, Folder 25)
      - Z- re Recommendations, Employment, etc., 1938-1942 (Box 22, Folder 26)
    - Sub-subseries 6: Speeches and Writings
      - MKS-Bibliography, ca.1937 (Box 22, Folder 27)
      - MKS- "Friendship and Politics", 1902 (Box 22, Folder 28)
      - MKS- Notes (numerous topics), 1904 (Box 22, Folder 29)
      - MKS- "Settlement Organization", 1906 (Box 22, Folder 30)
      - MKS- The Public School as a Neighborhood Club House-- Civic Forum Banquet, 1909 (Box 22, Folder 31)
      - MKS- Statement on Behalf of Equal Franchise Society, 1910 (Box 22, Folder 32)
      - MKS- Women's Invasion of the Industrial Field, 1910 (Box 22, Folder 33)
      - MKS- "Standard & Tests of Efficiency in Settlement Work" (reprinted from The Proceedings of the National Conference of Charities and Correction), 1911 (Box 22, Folder 34)
      - MKS- "Memorial to Henry Sylvester Nash" (letter to the editor-- New York Evening Post), 1912 (Box 22, Folder 35)
      - MKS- "A Word from Greenwich House" in Junior League Bulletin, 1913 (Box 22, Folder 36)
      - Isabel Dillingham Obituary (letter to the editor-- New York Evening Post), 1914 (Box 22, Folder 37)
      - MKS- Recreation and the Tax Budget-Citizens Protest Meeting, 1914 (Box 22, Folder 38)
      - MKS- The Citizen and His Neighborhood, 1915 (Box 22, Folder 39)
      - MKS- Community Organization, 1915 (Box 22, Folder 40)
      - MKS- Opening of Betsey Head Playground, 1915 (Box 22, Folder 41)
      - MKS- "The Settlement and Religion" in The Churchman, 1916 (Box 22, Folder 42)
      - MKS- "The Settlements and the War" (letter to the editor-- New York Evening Post), 1917 (Box 22, Folder 43)
      - MKS- The Settlement's Part in National Preparedness-- Northwestern University Settlement, 1917 (Box 22, Folder 44)
      - MKS- "The Settlement's Place in the Community Center Movement" in The Community Center, 1917 (Box 22, Folder 45)
      - MKS- "A Settlement War Program", 1917 (Box 22, Folder 46)
      - MKS- The Church and Woman Suffrage, 1917 (Box 22, Folder 47)
      - MKS- "The Need of an American Labor Party", 1919 (Box 22, Folder 48)
      - MKS- Memorandum re Lusk Bills, ca.1919 (Box 22, Folder 49)
      - MKS- speech on "The Child and the City", ca.1920 (Box 22, Folder 50)
      - MKS- "The Settlement Primer", 1926 (Box 22, Folder 51)
      - MKS- Statement on Goals in National Federation of Settlements Symposium, 1926 (Box 22, Folder 52)
      - MKS- "The Story of Greenwich House" (from 1927 Annual Report) (Box 22, Folder 53)
      - MKS- Correspondence- Macmillan Company, 1927-1944 (Box 22, Folder 54)
      - MKS- Do Women with College Educations and Who Follow Careers Make Less Home-Loving and Less Docile Wives?-- Daily Princetonian, 1928 (Box 22, Folder 55)
      - MKS- The School as a Neighborhood Center-- National Community Center Association Members' Bulletin, 1928 (Box 22, Folder 56)
      - MKS- "Al Smith- Able, Honest, Liberal" in The Nation", 1928 (Box 22, Folder 57)
      - MKS- Letter to the Editor endorsing Alfred E. Smith for President-- Dallas News, 1928 (Box 22, Folder 58)
      - MKS- Letters to the Editor endorsing Alfred E. Smith for President, 1928 (Box 22, Folder 59)
      - MKS- Statement endorsing Alfred E. Smith for President- The Nation?, 1928 (Box 22, Folder 60)
      - MKS- Defining "Settlement" ( Neighborhood), 1928 (Box 22, Folder 61)
      - MKS- Mexican Neighborliness, 1928 (Box 22, Folder 62)
      - MKS- Statement on Mexican Exhibit-- Staff News, Hudson Park Library, ca.1928 (Box 22, Folder 63)
      - MKS- Review of Mary McDowall New York Herald Tribune, 1929 (Box 22, Folder 64)
      - MKS- "Our Human Need of Art" in The Survey, 1929 (Box 22, Folder 65)
      - MKS- "Father Field" in Opportunity- Journal of Negro Life, 1930 (Box 22, Folder 66)
      - MKS- Biographical sketch of Charlotte Barnell Ware-- Kappa Kappa Gamma History, 1930 (Box 22, Folder 67)
      - MKS- The Place of the Art in the Settlement Program of Recreation National Conference of Social Work, 1930 (Box 22, Folder 68)
      - MKS- "The Greenwich House of Pottery" in Neighborhood, 1939 (Box 22, Folder 69)
      - MKS- The New Day in the Social and Industrial World, 1930 (Box 22, Folder 70)
      - MKS- "Jane Addams, World Citizen and Hull House Neighbor"-- New York Evening Post(book review), 1930 (Box 22, Folder 71)
      - "The Second Twenty Years of Hull House" by Jane Addams, 1930 (Box 22, Folder 72)
      - MKS- "The Changing Settlement" in Better Times, 1931 (Box 22, Folder 73)
      - MKS- What a Slum is and What it does, 1931 (Box 22, Folder 74)
      - MKS- Review of Problems of City Life-- The Saturday Review of Literature, 1932 (Box 22, Folder 75)
      - MKS- "The Christian Way Out" in The Witness, 1932 (Box 22, Folder 76)
      - MKS- The Womans Press-- interview and editorial, 1933 (Box 22, Folder 77)
      - MKS- Memorial Meeting to Felix Adler-- Ethical Culture School, 1933 (Box 22, Folder 78)
      - MKS- Changing Needs of the House in the New Era-- Address at Teachers College and article in Practical Home Economics, 1933 (Box 22, Folder 79)
      - MKS- Abstract of Detroit Address on Housing, 1933 (Box 22, Folder 80)
      - MKS- An Old New Dealer-- The Nation, 1933 (Box 22, Folder 81)
      - MKS- Leisure Time, 1933 (Box 22, Folder 82)
      - MKS- Statement Endorsing LaGuardia for Mayor, 1933 (Box 22, Folder 83)
      - MKS- Memorial Address on Felix Adler in The Statement, 1933 (Box 22, Folder 84)
      - MKS- re Greenwich House-- radio broadcast, 1933 (Box 22, Folder 85)
      - MKS- re Christianity and Social Welfare, 1933 (Box 22, Folder 86)
      - MKS- Social Action, 1933 (Box 22, Folder 87)
      - MKS- re Greenwich House, ca.1933 (Box 22, Folder 88)
      - MKS- Statement re Public Responsibility for Low-income Housing, ca.1933 (Box 22, Folder 89)
      - MKS- Introducing Governor Lehman-- WJZ, 1934 (Box 22, Folder 90)
      - MKS- Education and Recreation-- The Women's Division of Federation, 1934 (Box 22, Folder 91)
      - MKS- Housing as a Permanent Municipal Service Local Initiative and Federal Funds-- WEAF, 1934 (Box 22, Folder 92)
      - MKS- "The Church and Better Housing" in The Spirit of Missions, 1934 (Box 22, Folder 93)
      - MKS- "The Church and Public Housing", 1934 (Box 22, Folder 94)
      - MKS- Submission to First Anniversary issue of The Villager, 1934 (Box 22, Folder 95)
      - MKS- New Aspects in Community Planning-- Welfare Council of Wyoming Valley, 1934 (Box 22, Folder 96)
      - MKS- Statement re Arts and Crafts Exhibit-- United Neighborhood Houses of New York, 1934 (Box 22, Folder 97)
      - MKS- Civic Art Week-- WEAF, 1934 (Box 22, Folder 98)
      - MKS- Social Aspects of Housing-- National Public Housing Conference, 1934 (Box 22, Folder 99)
      - MKS- British Action in Slum Clearance-- reprinted from The New Republic, 1934 (Box 22, Folder 100)
      - MKS- Mothers and Daughters-- Church of the Holy Nativity, 1934 (Box 22, Folder 101)
      - MKS- New England Housing Conference-- National Radio Broadcast, 1934 (Box 22, Folder 102)
      - MKS- Youth and the Home-- WEVD, 1934 (Box 22, Folder 103)
      - MKS- in Support of Joseph McGoldrick for City Comptroller-- WOV, 1934 (Box 22, Folder 104)
      - MKS- Statement re Conference on Unemployment Insurance, 1934 (Box 22, Folder 105)
      - MKS- Tribute Dinner Address-- WJZ, 1934 (Box 22, Folder 106)
      - MKS- The Progress of Slum Clearance in New York-- The Living Church (with Elizabeth Ogg), 1934 (Box 22, Folder 107)
      - MKS- The Future of Relief ( Better Times), 1934 (Box 22, Folder 108)
      - MKS- re Work Relief and Home Relief-- Welfare Council of New York City, 1934 (Box 22, Folder 109)
      - MKS- God's Crisis-- YWCA, 1934 (Box 22, Folder 110)
      - MKS- "The Red Festival", 1934 (Box 22, Folder 111)
      - MKS- re Tenement Legislation, ca.1935 (Box 22, Folder 112)
      - MKS- Social Gains and Promise-- WJZ, 1935 (Box 22, Folder 113)
      - MKS- What the Forum Means to the Voter-- WNYC, 1935 (Box 22, Folder 114)
      - MKS- The Present Status of European Housing, 1935 (Box 22, Folder 115)
      - MKS- What's Next in Housing-- WQXR, 1935 (Box 22, Folder 116)
      - MKS- Third National Public Housing Conference-- Radio Address, 1936 (Box 23, Folder 1)
        Reel 27 (MN# 2208)
      - MKS- Public Housing in 1936-- Brooklyn Daily Eagle (Box 23, Folder 2)
      - MKS- Federation of Jewish Women's Organization, 1936 (Box 23, Folder 3)
      - MKS- Value of Settlement Houses-- Radio Broadcast, 1936 (Box 23, Folder 4)
      - MKS- Forces Making For and Against Centralization in the United States-- International Federation of the Settlements, 1936 (Box 23, Folder 5)
      - MKS- Submission to the Third Birthday Celebration Edition-- The Villager, 1936 (Box 23, Folder 6)
      - MKS- Statement to Committee Hearing on Wagner and Ellenbogen Bill, 1936 (Box 23, Folder 7)
      - MKS- Wagner Public House Bill-- WEVD, 1936 (Box 23, Folder 8)
      - MKS- Kiwanis Address, 1936 (Box 23, Folder 9)
      - MKS- The Boy and His House-- WEAF, 1936 (Box 23, Folder 10)
      - MKS- Article on Slum Clearance and Housing-- The Woman Today, 1936 (Box 23, Folder 11)
      - MKS- Adult Education in Informal Institutions, 1936 (Box 23, Folder 12)
      - MKS- Slums as a Social Menace-- WHN, 1936 (Box 23, Folder 13)
      - MKS- Boston University Alumni Sunset Supper, 1936 (Box 23, Folder 14)
      - MKS- Statement Endorsing Re-election of Franklin Roosevelt, 1936 (Box 23, Folder 15)
      - MKS- Why You Should Vote for the New Charter-- WHN, 1936 (Box 23, Folder 16)
      - MKS- I Vote for Roosevelt ( The Witness), 1936 (Box 23, Folder 17)
      - MKS- A.W.A. Speech re Democracy, Liberalism, Roosevelt, 1936 (Box 23, Folder 18)
      - MKS- Statement Endorsing Re-election of Franklin Roosevelt, 1936 (Box 23, Folder 19)
      - MKS- re Social Work, Liberalism, Political Issues, 1936 (Box 23, Folder 20)
      - MKS- My Happiest Christmas Experience ( The Churchman), 1936 (Box 23, Folder 21)
      - MKS- Fifty Years of the Settlement in New York-- National Federation of Settlements, 1936 (Box 23, Folder 22)
      - MKS- Greetings to Delegates of Kappa Kappa Gamma Convention, 1936 (Box 23, Folder 23)
      - MKS- "The Settlement Primer" (second edition), 1936 (Box 23, Folder 24)
      - MKS- Statement re Wagner- Ellenbogen Public Housing Bill, ca.1936 (Box 23, Folder 25)
      - MKS- re Demolition and Construction of Housing and Wagner Bill, ca.1936 (Box 23, Folder 26)
      - MKS- re Slum Clearance and Rebuilding, ca.1936 (Box 23, Folder 27)
      - MKS- City Hall Radio Address, 1937 (Box 23, Folder 28)
      - MKS- How Far Ought Social Workers Go in Espousing Social Causes-- Better Times, 1937 (Box 23, Folder 29)
      - MKS- The Housing Fog is Lifting-- Radio Address, 1937 (Box 23, Folder 30)
      - MKS- re Summer Vacations-- American Childhood, 1937 (Box 23, Folder 31)
      - MKS- Statement for Social Work Today Brochure, 1937 (Box 23, Folder 32)
      - MKS- Address at Memorial Meeting for Dr. Henry Moskowitz, 1937 (Box 23, Folder 33)
      - MKS- Statement re "On Journey" by Vida Scudder, 1937 (Box 23, Folder 34)
      - MKS- "Faith for Every Day" in The Holy Cross Magazine, 1937 (Box 23, Folder 35)
      - MKS- City Council Campaign Statement-- WEVD, 1937 (Box 23, Folder 36)
      - MKS- National Public Housing Conference, ca.1937 (Box 23, Folder 37)
      - MKS- re Portrait, ca.1937 (Box 23, Folder 38)
      - MKS- "Thirty-five Years at Greenwich House", ca.1937 (Box 23, Folder 39)
      - MKS- Address given at Opening of Housing Course at New York University, 1938 (Box 23, Folder 40)
      - MKS-Articles and Book Reviews re "Neighborhood: My Story of Greenwich House", 1938 (Box 23, Folder 41)
      - Neighborhood-- Correspondence, 1932-1936 (Box 23, Folder 42)
      - Neighborhood-- Correspondence-- W.W. Norton & Co., 1937-1943 (Box 23, Folder 43)
      - MKS- Review of My Days by Eleanor Roosevelt-- Book Mark, 1938 (Box 23, Folder 44)
      - MKS- Election Statement re Housing and Governor Lehman-- WMCA, 1938 (Box 23, Folder 45)
      - MKS- re Public Housing and Settlements, 1938 (Box 23, Folder 46)
      - MKS- Introduction to Musical Performances-- WABC, 1939 (Box 23, Folder 47)
      - MKS- Address to the First Church in Newton, Massachusetts, 1939 (Box 23, Folder 48)
      - MKS- Seligman Memorial, 1939 (Box 23, Folder 49)
      - MKS- re Death of Poor Person, 1930s (Box 23, Folder 50)
      - MKS- re Public Housing Subsidies (letter to the editor, New York Post), 1940 (Box 23, Folder 51)
      - MKS- Review of Group Life in Christian Century, 1940 (Box 23, Folder 52)
      - MKS- Tenth Annual Meeting, Public Housing Conference, 1941 (Box 23, Folder 53)
      - MKS- Keeping Up With the Jones' -- Social Work Today, 1941 (Box 23, Folder 54)
      - MKS- Neighborhood Planning-- National Federation of Settlements, 1941 (Box 23, Folder 55)
      - MKS- V for Victory Meeting, 1941 (Box 23, Folder 56)
      - MKS- Statement at Groundbreaking Exercises, Ft. Greene Houses, 1941 (Box 23, Folder 57)
      - MKS- re Special Service During Wartime-- Social Work Today, 1942 (Box 23, Folder 58)
      - MKS- A Laywoman's Comments on Joint Ordination-- The Witness, 1942 (Box 23, Folder 59)
      - MKS- League of Friendship-- The Villager, 1942 (Box 23, Folder 60)
      - MKS- re Abraham Epstein, Association for Social Security-- Better Times, 1942 (Box 23, Folder 61)
      - MKS- John Lovejoy Elliott-- Better Times, 1942 (Box 23, Folder 62)
      - MKS- re Federal Housing Activities-- New York Times, 1942 (Box 23, Folder 63)
      - MKS- South American Broadcast, 1942 (Box 23, Folder 64)
      - MKS- Toward a More Democratic Neighborhood Organization-- Compass, ca.1942 (Box 23, Folder 64A)
      - MKS- re Women and Defense Work (letter to the Editor, New York Times), 1943 (Box 23, Folder 65)
      - MKS- Untitled Talk on Childcare at First Meeting of Women's Home Service, 1943 (Box 23, Folder 66)
      - MKS- "Neighborhood and Nation", 1944 (Box 23, Folder 67)
      - MKS- The Neighborhood as a Social Unit", 1944 (Box 23, Folder 68)
      - MKS- Obituary of Edith Elmer Wood, 1945 (Box 23, Folder 69)
      - MKS- Untitled Address to Board of Directors on Zoning, 1945 (Box 23, Folder 70)
      - MKS- "Neighborhoods and Planning", ca.1945 (Box 23, Folder 71)
      - MKS- Speech at her Retirement, 1946 (Box 23, Folder 72)
      - MKS- City Hall Speech re Housing, 1946 (Box 23, Folder 73)
      - MKS- Report on Housing-- WLIB, 1946 (Box 23, Folder 74)
      - MKS- Address at Memorial Meeting for FDR, 1947 (Box 23, Folder 75)
      - MKS- Memorial to Fiorello LaGuardia (Letter to the Editor-- New York Herald Tribune), 1947 (Box 23, Folder 76)
      - MKS- Address at the Laying of the Cornerstone of The Lillian Wald Houses, 1947 (Box 23, Folder 77)
      - MKS- "In our Part of Town"-- Survey Midmonthly, 1947 (Box 23, Folder 78)
      - MKS- Statement to National Public Housing Conference, 1948 (Box 23, Folder 79)
      - MKS- Settlements in 1950 (Box 23, Folder 80)
      - MKS- Dedicatory notes on United Neighborhood Houses, 1951 (Box 23, Folder 81)
      - MKS- Karl Barth, undated (Box 23, Folder 82)
      - MKS- The Case Work Plane, undated (Box 23, Folder 83)
      - MKS- re Church and Abolition of Slums, undated (Box 23, Folder 84)
      - MKS- Review of book The Church and the Hour by Vida D. Scudder, undated (Box 23, Folder 85)
      - MKS- The Conscientious Objector, undated (Box 23, Folder 86)
      - MKS- re Divorce and Christianity, undated (Box 23, Folder 87)
      - MKS- Easter-- A Modern Mystery Tale, undated (Box 23, Folder 88)
      - MKS- Economic Difficulties in Rural Maine, undated (Box 23, Folder 89)
      - MKS- Educational Alliance, undated (Box 23, Folder 90)
      - MKS- The Extension of Neighborhood Work in Our Public Educational System, undated (Box 23, Folder 91)
      - MKS- Greenwich House, undated (Box 23, Folder 92)
      - MKS- Greenwich House, undated (Box 23, Folder 93)
      - MKS- Housing, undated (Box 23, Folder 94)
      - MKS- Housing Management in England, undated (Box 23, Folder 95)
      - MKS- How to Arouse Civic Interest in Children, undated (Box 23, Folder 96)
      - MKS- Interview re Housing, undated (Box 23, Folder 97)
      - MKS- The Jewish Question - A Christian Question, undated (Box 23, Folder 98)
      - MKS- The Key-- Fiftieth Anniversary, undated (Box 23, Folder 99)
      - MKS- The Life and Witness of the Christian Community, undated (Box 23, Folder 100)
      - MKS- Statement in Support of Masses, undated (Box 23, Folder 100A)
      - MKS- re Mediocrity, Education, Settlements, undated (Box 23, Folder 101)
      - MKS- Statement Endorsing Newbold Morris for President of the Board of Aldermen, undated (Box 23, Folder 102)
      - MKS- National Convention Plank re Federal Aid, undated (Box 23, Folder 103)
      - MKS- The Near East Turns a Corner, undated (Box 23, Folder 104)
      - MKS- Opening Address-- National Federation of Settlements, undated (Box 23, Folder 105)
      - MKS- Recreation Through Art, undated (Box 23, Folder 106)
      - MKS- A Sermon by any Bishop at the Consecration of any Other, undated (Box 23, Folder 107)
      - MKS- "Settlement Catechism", undated (Box 23, Folder 108)
      - MKS- re Settlements and Neighborhood Life, undated (Box 23, Folder 109)
      - MKS- The Social Centre in Cities, undated (Box 23, Folder 110)
      - MKS- Social Education versus Social Work, undated (Box 23, Folder 111)
      - MKS- re Social Work Visitors, undated (Box 23, Folder 112)
      - MKS- Suggestions for Club Leaders, undated (Box 23, Folder 113)
      - MKS- The Trend of the Social Settlement, undated (Box 23, Folder 114)
      - MKS- A Unique Quiet Day-- Lincoln's Birthday Conference for Social Workers, undated (Box 23, Folder 115)
      - MKS- Women and the Church-- The Witness, undated (Box 23, Folder 116)
      - VGS- "Carola Woerishoffer- In Memoriam" (reprinted from The Survey), 1911 (Box 23, Folder 117)
      - Book Review of Marxism Versus Socialism by Vladimir G. Simkhovitch and The Truth About Socialism by Allan L. Benson-- New York Times, 1913 (Box 23, Folder 118)
    - Sub-subseries 7: Financial (Personal)
      - Monthly Budget, ca.1928-1938 (Box 23, Folder 119)
      - Sunset Lodge Corporation, 1925-1938 (Box 23, Folder 120)
      - Women's University Club Realty Co.-- Correspondence, 1928 (Box 23, Folder 121)
      - Inventories of Securities, 1928, 1931 (Box 23, Folder 122)
      - Brokerage Statements and Correspondence, 1928-1930 (Box 23, Folder 123)
      - re Estate of Laura D.H. Kingsbury, 1930, 1932-1933 (Box 23, Folder 124)
      - Trust Agreement with The Travelers Bank and Trust Company, 1919 (Box 23, Folder 125)
      - The Travelers Bank and Trust Company-- Principal Statements, 1928-1943 (Box 23, Folder 126)
      - The Travelers Bank and Trust Company-- Income Statements, 1928-1938 (Box 23, Folder 127)
      - The Travelers Bank and Trust Company-- Income Statements, 1938-1943 (Box 23, Folder 128)
      - Correspondence with The Travelers Bank and Trust Company, 1937-1939 (Box 23, Folder 129)
      - Equitable Life Assurance Society-- Correspondence, 1938 (Box 23, Folder 130)
  - Subseries B: Staff
    - Sub-subseries 1: Robin Brown
      - Correspondence, 1942-1944 (Box 23, Folder 131)
    - Sub-subseries 2: Marian Porter
      - Correspondence, 1914-1915 (Box 23, Folder 132)
      - Correspondence, undated, ca.1914-1915) (Box 23, Folder 133)
    - Sub-subseries 3: Mabel Spinney
      - Correspondence, 1916 (Box 23, Folder 134)
      - Correspondence, 1915 (Box 23, Folder 135)
        Reel 28 (MN# 2209)
      - Correspondence, 1916 (Box 23, Folder 136)
      - Correspondence, 1917 (Box 23, Folder 137)
- Series III: Programs
  Organization: Series III: Programs
  Subseries A: Departments and Activities
  Sub-subseries 1: General --House Information, Rules and Schedules
  Sub-subseries 2: Adult Education Project
  Sub-subseries 3: Alumni
  Sub-subseries 4: Americanization Work
  Sub-subseries 5: Art
  Sub-subseries 6: Assistant Director
  Sub-subseries 7: Athletics
  Sub-subseries 8: Board of Delegates
  Sub-subseries 9: Boys' and Men's Work
  Sub-subseries 10: Camps
  Sub-subseries 11: Children's Work
  Sub-subseries 12: Clubs
  Sub-subseries 13: Conferences
  Sub-subseries 14: Donations
  Sub-subseries 15: Ella Sachs Plotz Memorial Library
  Sub-subseries 16: Employment Department
  Sub-subseries 17: English classes
  Sub-subseries 18: Evening activities